<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-01-28T20:22:50+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Aptitude Business Consulting</title><subtitle>Providing Project Management and Business Analysis solutions to meet your needs</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Lee Clarke - Dynama Solutions</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/testimonials/Lee-Clarke-Dynama/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Lee Clarke - Dynama Solutions" /><published>2020-05-09T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2021-01-28T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/testimonials/Lee-Clarke-Dynama</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/testimonials/Lee-Clarke-Dynama/">&lt;p&gt;I have worked with Dan on a professional basis for several years.  As a Consultant, Dan is exceptional in his attention to detail and great in dealing with end users who know what they want but can’t always translate that into workable requirements.  As a Project Manager, Dan is not only qualified, but brings many years experience working with a range of organisations.  As anyone who has worked on larger projects can tell you, good governance, informed stakeholders and clear objectives are essential in achieving successful outcomes.  Dan communicates risks clearly and helps navigate obstacles that invariably appear in projects and does so in a professional and respectful way.  When I have needed flexibility, Dan has provided it.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="Testimonials" /><summary type="html">I have worked with Dan on a professional basis for several years. As a Consultant, Dan is exceptional in his attention to detail and great in dealing with end users who know what they want but can’t always translate that into workable requirements. As a Project Manager, Dan is not only qualified, but brings many years experience working with a range of organisations. As anyone who has worked on larger projects can tell you, good governance, informed stakeholders and clear objectives are essential in achieving successful outcomes. Dan communicates risks clearly and helps navigate obstacles that invariably appear in projects and does so in a professional and respectful way. When I have needed flexibility, Dan has provided it.</summary></entry></feed>